Jai Hind friends, please read the disclaimer.
I am not a SEBI registered advisor
friends.  We will talk about many companies in this video.  We will
talk about HCL, about HDFC.  We will
talk about ICICI LBRD and many more
coaching platforms.  Let's
talk about SWGI.  Many
companies have received orders.  Many
important updates are coming out.  Let's
say latest, some updates have also
come related to results and dividends.   There have been
many updates regarding the results.
But I am especially covering the dividend ones
because they are big companies.   There
are good companies.  Okay, right?  First of all,
two news are coming out in Swiggy
and these are the news after the market close.
Its current market price is ₹450.
This company is trading at a valuation of ₹11000 crores.  First of all, this
company is doing one thing that it is transferring its Instagram
brand.  One is
forming its step down subsidiary wholly owned company which is
transferring the shares of Here Pay through a slump sale to the buyer SW Sorry W OS by making a swig instam which is Here Pay Private Limited.
So, let's say the Instagram
brand of Swiggi, there is a plan to transfer it here in this manner
and there is another news related to the same, let's say it was
Repdo, this Instagram, this
was a news related to Swiggi, so it is going to transfer its Instagram brand to Swigg Instam Private
Limited,
right,
under that, all its assets, liabilities,
permits, licenses, records, wicked, whatever
property it has, everything will be transferred.  By forming a new
company, a new branded type
company will be formed.  Okay, right?  One
news is coming that they have approved the sale of a total of 35958
compulsorily convertible
preference shares.
Meaning, let us say here that they have made an agreement to sell their entire stake in Rapido, including the compulsory
convertible preferential shares that the company
had.
With whom?  Along the Brest Bridge.
It is already a shareholder in Rapido in the same,
Breastwich is already a shareholder and you can
say that Swiggy is also a shareholder
through preference shares.  Okay, right
?  So now they are
preparing to sell their stake in Breast Wiz and have made this
agreement.  Okay, right?  Now it is being
told here that a share purchase agreement has been made
for Swiggy.  Here is the Setu
AIF Trust and its partners
called Breast Witch.  Okay, right?  Breast witch
is okay, right?  It is being told that the stake that Total is going to
sell is going to be sold for Rs 431 crore
49 lakh 60 thousand.
What is mentioned here is that the same 35968
CCPS
Compulsory Convertible Preference Shares.
Okay, right?  Its full form will be.  So
look at it this way.  However, when I went to
search for it while I was reading the news, I
found another news in
which a slightly different value was being told.
Swiggy will sell its stake in Rapido to
Process and Best Wiz Capital for around ₹400
crore.  So here, whatever is
different, it has been told that the value is ₹400 crores.
So look at it this way,
overall you can understand that Swiggy will be
in focus tomorrow.  There can be a rise as well as a
fall.  Especially the possibility of rise will be
high.  ICICI LBR General
Insurance is trading at ₹100 its current market price.
Brother, the company's
result is going to come first, on 14 October 2025, the
company's result will come here for Q2, along with this the
company is giving interim dividend,
hence I am covering it.  Will
also consider dividend.  The record date fixed by the company
for dividend is
17 October 2025.
Okay, right?  So please take a look at this.
I will let you know if any other updates come.  HCL
Technology LED is also trading at ₹1430.  The
result date of this company has also been announced.
Now its result for 13 October 2025 will
come and this company is also going to give its third interim dividend.  I am
covering this as well.
Naveen Fluorine International is
seen trading at its current price of ₹4692.  Let us simply
say that this company will also have
stand loan and consolidated result.
Along with this, the company is also going to give interim dividend on
30 October 2025.  Along with this,
HDFC Bank LED is also seen trading at a current price of ₹957.  The
results of this company are also about to come brother.
Consolidated and unaudited
standalone results will also be released.  Besides,
this company is also probably going to give us dividend.
Somewhere I was reading dividends.  It is
not written here brother.  So please take a
look at this also.  Okay, right?  There
is a company along with it.  What is its name now
?  Here it is written in Hindi Sensis
LED.  SSIS LED is this company.  SSIS TH LED is
trading at ₹1600 current price.
Brother, this company has received an order of ₹16
crores in which it is said that it has got the
agreement from Mumbai Metropolitan Region Development Authority (MMRDA).
They have signed a purchase agreement for software production enterprise agreement by doing ESRE Arc GIS in MMRDA.  This is
how it is picked here.  You guys should
see this.  Looks like a good order is
coming.  Just understand the value that the
company has received an order worth ₹16 crores.   This is an
order placed after the market closes.
So this stock will also be in focus tomorrow.  Okay, right
?  A good news is coming out from Cochin Shipyard.  It
is a government company.  This is also a good company brother.
Its current trading price is ₹1885.  It has partnered with HD Korea to
build ships in India at Cochin Shipyard.  The
total investment that is going to be made is going to be
₹3700 crores.  We are going to set up another manufacturing unit in 80 acres.  According to me, it will have a
capacity of six ships.
So, this is what has been told by the Government of India.
See, this
is also official news.  According to me, it was inaugurated by Prime Minister Modi on
20th September.  In
this way, taking forward the steps towards self-reliant India,
this agreement has been made
with the Korean company.
HD Korea Shipbuilding & Offshore
Engineering Ltd.  That means it also does ship
building work.  So,
under Making India, it has been installed here.
This will be made further.  Okay, right?   This
means that if this plant is set up, ships will be
manufactured in it.  It has been told
that the capacity to build approximately six ships will be
built here in a year.
In which the initial investment will be Rs 1500 crore.
But the total investment in this is going to be ₹700
crores.  Okay, right?
You guys can see it this way.  This is great
news.  This stock will also be in focus tomorrow.   Please
note it down and keep it.  Okay, right?